A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
It's not far off. We're here.
It's not far off.
It's far off.
No openings.
What now?
Medusa hasn't made any attempts at all to put an end to this fight.
She's just trying to buy time by keeping us occupied here.
She's an intuitive witch.
She probably knows that I won't be able to defeat her if my head is full of disturbing thoughts.
Stein, what's going on with you?
It seems like you're losing your edge.
What happened to that ominous I'll kill you vibe you used to give off?
Quiet spirit.
That's exactly what I'm trying to work on right now.
I'm paying too much attention to everything that's going on around me.
I need to get rid of irrelevant thoughts.
What drives me is curiosity.
I always do my best work when the subject at hand intrigues me.
That's what I need to focus on.
The tension is starting to leave his body.
He may be the DWMA's greatest Meister.
He's an easy guy to read if you know what to look for.
What is it I want to do, you ask?
I would think it obvious.
It's obvious you're a sadistic man, Stein.
I want to dissect.
Dead or alive in the rift between Revival and Dazzlement?
Oh Stein, you're so adorable.
Yeah.
I almost forgot it's my job to control this head case.
What's this fool up to now?
Please, no more. I'm begging you.
I'm gonna tear you into little pieces.
I wonder how I should do it though.
Cut up or gouge out or simply rip apart.
That's for later though.
Right now I'll give you a painless death.
Step away.
I think that's enough, don't you?
Stay out of this spirit.
I'm going to do things my way.
So then what?
You're just going to ignore all the Academy's rules?
Well, what is it you want to do?
Did you think you could simply do anything you please once you were in the DWMA?
I wish I lived in a world that knew nothing of the gods.
Whoa, whoa.
Do you seriously mean that?
Of course not.
A world like that would be...
diseased.
I'll say it again, Professor Stein.
Join my experiment.
This static, unchanging world doesn't suit you.
You were made for better than this.
You're a scientist after all.
We can harness the power of the Kishin together.
We'll change the world back to what it should be.
A place where evolution and progress always reign.
A long time ago.
I was analyzed by a group of foolish doctors who feared my violent tendencies and what they considered my selfish attitude.
They seemed elated while they were studying me.
As if they were solving the crime in a mystery novel they theorized for hours.
Wondering if something had traumatized me in my past.
Or if some terrible influence had come into my life.
That was all nonsense though.
I've loved tearing things apart from the very beginning.
What's your point, Stein?
Are you trying to compare me to these doctors?
When I was in kindergarten it made me nauseous watching the other kids as they listened dutifully to the teacher and played games.
I would almost puke just from the sight of everyone focusing unquestioningly on the chalkboard while they took their notes.
Not an original thought in their heads.
What kind of story is this anyway?
It's entirely pointless not to mention boring.
Makes me want to puke.
Are you mocking me?
If you hate unoriginality so much why are your attacks so tiresome?
Really, I'm sleeping here.
Now, now, be more patient.
This is my answer to your invitation so you should listen.
My feelings didn't change as I matured and grew stronger.
The madness inside of me, the desire to dissect it too.
Do you know what it was that eventually stopped me?
It was fear.
Yes, I was terrified.
Terrified of the person I might become.
Even though all that mattered to me in the end was that I had fun and could do whatever I wanted.
That's when I learned that I needed someone in control.
Not a greedy despot who would rule with tyrannical disregard for the wants and needs of others.
But the rule of a god. One who reigned without ego.
If you hate this world so much, why not join me? We can change the world together.
That's your ego talking now, isn't it?
No. But following one's own ego will become the standard before long.
A standard you too will follow.
Stein!
You can't attack without thinking. She'll keep striking you down if you do.
If this new standard you're talking about does come to pass, what will control my dark side then?
I can never join you in this.
I suppose there's no getting through to you.
I want to tear things apart without losing my soul!
So that's how you choose to use your madness, huh?
What?
So far!
Got her.
But still, he took on way too much damage for just a single hit.
I think I've been overestimating you, Stein.
That flimsy attack is all you could manage after turning down such a gracious invitation.
It's all over.
I think I'll remove your head now.
Spirit, listen. Not a single move.
What the? My tail snake stopped.
I can't move anything.
Soul thread. Diffusion sutures.
What are you talking about?
You haven't even sewn my body to anything yet.
Take a closer look.
The threads are sewn throughout the inside of your body as well.
I'm using them to block every nerve ending you have so you're completely paralyzed.
What are you waiting for?
Why don't you kill me with a hit from your scythe friend there?
You're running out of time, remember?
Controlling such an enormous wavelength takes total concentration.
Focusing on that requires all my energy. I can't move a single finger.
This is pathetic, even for a last ditch effort.
Are you improvising or is this how you always like to fight?
What's your plan? A Wild West shootout the instant you release these threads?
Don't you see how pointless it is?
My snake is already at your neck.
It'll lop your head off before your scythe even has a chance to touch me.
I somehow doubt that wavelength control of this magnitude can last for very long.
Think about it. As soon as it's released you will die.
And the Kishin will be reborn at last.
You don't stand a chance against me now.
That's it.
That?
Yeah, the bag over there.
I wouldn't be surprised if it was an object of worship or something before it sucked up the Kishin's madness.
Now it looks like this.
All set.
This is it.
The black blood is in that syringe!
Take this!
There we go!
What?
Damn!
Who's this mummy guy?
He's been caught in the madness like we were.
Now's our chance.
Right!
Damn it! Not this again.
I'm really getting sick of this guy.
I feel like I'm starting to lose it!
Calm down. Just breathe.
What you're seeing is brought on by the wavelength of the Kishin's madness.
You've felt it plenty of times on the way down here.
It's only a hallucination!
She's got the blood!
This sure hurts more than it did earlier!
As long as I'm aiming for the black blood, the werewolf won't be able to move!
I'll cover you, Blackstar! Go now!
I'm going!
Be careful. The Kishin's madness can make you hallucinate!
No worries on that one. My six sense really sucks!
I can barely feel the madness at all!
Excellent!
It's coming, Erika!
And Janet!
And Janet, the future hurts more than it did earlier!
The future hurts more than it did earlier!
As long as I'm aiming for the black blood, the werewolf won't be able to move!
I'll cover you, Blackstar! Go now!
I'm going!
Be careful. The Kishin's madness can make you hallucinate!
No worries on that one. My six sense really sucks!
I can barely feel the madness at all!
Excellent.
It's coming, Erika!
Enchanted sword mode!
Krivet bomb, krivet crop. Pro krivet, croak, croak!
Try one of my tadpole bombs!
Alright! Don't even try!
It's just a hallucination! Just a hallucination!
Here goes!
Hey! Don't do it! No!
Take this!
What?
Good job, boy!
You didn't find the amphibian getting in my way!
Temple Jackson!
You were a good pet! I won't forget you!
Damn! Don't even think about it! Get the hell away from there, frog girl!
No!
Hurry up, Erika!
You've gotta stop it now, Blackstar!
The enchanted sword mode is at its limit!
But I have to do this, even if it tears me apart!
Even if it tears me apart!
Come on! Hurry!
Please, just go in!
Looks like your time is up, froggy!
Take this!
冷!
Eh!
I did it!
We won!
There's no Kishin reviving today.
This is a gamble, and the odds are stacked against us.
We can't hold this forever.
The only way to beat Medusa is to take the offensive somehow and strike at her.
We've come this far, we're just a step away.
The moment those sutures come undone, the fight will start all over again.
And as Medusa said, I'm likely to be the loser.
Her tail is pointed at my throat just a hair's breath away from beheading me.
But right now I can't seem to picture myself being defeated.
All I can imagine is dismembering that witch.
Dissection is what I do best.
My only chance is to roll the dice and hope I win.
What's happening?
What is that?
The Kishin's madness is overflowing.
That means kids' group couldn't stop them.
The Kishin is reviving.
Free, we succeeded.
No, this can't be happening.
Hold on a sec.
But we won, didn't we?
Your desperation wound up working against us.
Take a closer look.
What you actually cut was the shrine sealing the bag.
What?
It's sort of ironic.
You were so focused on destroying the syringe that you left yourself vulnerable.
Your sixth sense kicked in and took over when you weren't expecting it.
At the very end, you must have begun hallucinating.
No, that...
That can't be right.
We've failed.
We couldn't stop it.
It looks like your kitty's failed.
The taste of victory is very sweet.
You did it.
I don't believe it.
It's gonna punch.
You can't help.
It's un architectural effect.
Let's think he got it.
So I can't find the...
.
The moment you were certain you had won, your blind elation gave me the opening I needed to defeat you.
It's ironic, really.
I only won because of the Kishin.
But now the demon has revived.
So in the end, I lose.
But still, I have to admit destroying you was refreshing.
Dammit, no!
Die!
That did nothing.
It's starting to come out!
Help me!
It's starting to come out.
The bag... the Kishin is putting its skin back on.
shark
and a venom on the habe.
humans
It starts with you and me
The door opens the door
What kind of future will you wait for me?
As long as you can see
だからあともう少しだけって
子供でいたい
Boys and girls
が何人もこのように隠れひそ
では夢を見ているっていうStory
Thank you all so much
As of today, I'm Medusa
I'm retiring
I'm sad to be leaving
But I have no regrets
After all, I did win
My experiment was a complete success
So what could I have to regret?
I mean, I suppose I do wish
I could have caused a bit more trouble
At the DWMA
And maybe talked to the Keysha
And toyed with Stein a little more
But all in all, nope, no regrets
Sounds like you might have one or two
On the next episode of Soul Eater
The Battle of the Gods
Death City on the verge of collapse?
Watch it, or I'll take your soul
And peace
?
the helicopter